Zongzhen (Jack) Yang

Highly motivated Computer Science and Communication Arts student with 5+ years' experience in VR/AR. A passionate team player who strives to make a difference in how people perceive the world and eagers to gain new experience.

jackyangzzh@gmail.com 862-400-3570 jackyang.space

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF WISCONSIN - MADISON

B.A. in Computer Science & Communication Arts

Teaching Assistant for CS559 Computer Graphics

SETON HALL PREPARATORY SCHOOL

National Honor Society

SKILLS

Virtual Reality

Unity • Leap Motion • Open VR • Oculus kit • Data Visualization • VR Design • SketchUp • Blender • THREE.js • Motion Tracking • ARkit • ARCore • 3D Modeling • Xcode

Programming Languages

C • C# • C++ • Java • JavaScript • HTML • CSS • MATLAB • Latex • Swift • Git • Vis.js

User Experience Design

Interaction Design • Usability Testing • Sketch • Adobe XD • Photoshop • 3D UX Design

Communication

Team Communication • Public Speaking • Presentation • Negotiation • Professional Writing • Cross-cultural Communication

COURSE WORK

Computer Science

Computer Graphics
Data Visualization
Artificial Intelligence
Wearable Technology
User Experience Design
User Interface Design
Game Design
Software Engineering

Communication Arts

Persuasion and Speeches Online Communication Dale Carnegie Training

RESEARCH

KATS LABATORY OF APPLIED PHYSICS

RESEARCH ASSISTANT

October 2017 - Present

- Design different algorithms to simulate different color visions including colorblindness
- Create and program Virtual Reality spaces to visualize research findings through color calibrated VR headsets

UW COMPUTER GRAPHICS LAB

RESEARCH ASSISTANT

September 2019 - Present

- Display and simulate robots' motion and activities in Virtual Reality setting through Unity
- Gather data from experiments by recording head/hand motion and eye tracker

UW HUMAN COMPUTER INTERACTION LAB

RESEARCH ASSISTANT

April 2017 - November 2017

- · Work on a robot that help elementary school children to read
- Develop an algorithm that rank books the readers are mostly likely to be interested in based on history and preferences
- Collaborate with engineers to add speech recognition and feedback features to robots

EXPERIENCE

HOLOS

UNITY DEVELOPER INTERN

May 2019 - Now

- Work with Unity and Leap Motion hand tracking to develop Virtual Reality platform for interactive learning
- Collaborate with CTO and co-founder to design, prototype, implement, and maintain interaction mechanics such as virtual objects and augmented gestures
- Develop multiplayer virtual reality environment for content sharing

CARNEGIE MELLON UNIVERSITY GAME ACADEMY

PRODUCT MANAGER & DEVELOPER

May 2015 - August 2015

- Develop two arcade-inspired game and an interactive Virtual Reality called Kitchen Kraving (soon to be published on Oculus store)
- Work with Maya to create 3D models and implement player interaction with Unity to create realistic player's virtual experience